(Raj:)to let people in.
(Sheldon:)Listen to what Mr. Wil
Wheaton is tweeting.
"Best seats in house
for Raiders screening.
Suck on that, Sheldon Cooper."
(Leonard:)Why do you read
his Twitter feed?
(Leonard:)You know it's only
going to upset you.
(Sheldon:)I believe in knowing
my enemy, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Had Twitter existed at the time,
would not General Custer
(Sheldon:)have followed the tweets
of Sitting Bull?
(Sheldon:)Would not Lee have
followed Grant?
(Sheldon:)Would not Spy have followed Spy?
(Sheldon:)I have more examples,
but excuse me.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Sheldon:)Well, this seems
like an odd time
(Sheldon:)to test my cell phone quality,
but go on.
(Sheldon:)Test phrases? All right.
(Sheldon:)Imatote.
Ulba.
(Sheldon:)Twad.
(Sheldon:)All together?
(Sheldon:)I'm a total buttwad.
(Sheldon:)Why are you laughing?